yoybuy.com 2019-06-10

# YOYbuy: Taobao Agent| The best shopping agent in China| Buy from taobao.com

##  Privacy Statement

Yoybuy respect your privacy. This Privacy Statement informs you how we collect and handle your personal information which you provide to us as you access and interact with this Website. 

**Information collected**

The information about you which we may collect through this Web Site varies depending on how you use this Web Site. We will collect information through any electronic forms you submit via this Web Site, or other messages you send us by e-mail. 

We may collect the personal details you submit on our site, such as name and email, mobile phone number, address, etc. Or other information we communicate by email, telephone, live chat sessions,  or alternate electronic or paper communication. 

In common with many websites, we may collect information such as the date and time of your visit to this Web Site, the pages accessed and any information downloaded. This information does not identify you as an individual and is used for statistical, reporting and Web Site administration and maintenance purposes only. Should you wish to no longer receive our mail, you may click on the unsubscribe link within each promotional email received and/or contact us at service@yoybuy.com. 

**Retargeting Policy**

YOYBUY.com collects non-personally identifiable information about your activities when you visit our website. This information may include the content you view, the products you purchased and so forth. We use the information collected to serve you more relevant advertisements (referred to as "Retargeting"). 

In case that you don't want to be retargeted any more, you can opt-out from Google's [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads) or simply delete all your cookies in your browser. Usually it is in Settings or history tab. 

**How we use your information**

The information Yoybuy collects to understand your needs and interests to help Yoybuy provide a better service. For example, Yoybuy may use your information to 

- complete a transaction or order; 

- allow you to participate in surveys and promotions; 

- prevent and detect fraud or other malicious activity; 

- improve or update our services; 

- help you solve some problems concerning our service or website; 

**How we share your information**

Yoybuy may provide personal information to 

- our service providers who assist us in providing this Web Site and our services (for example internet and technology service providers, mail houses, delivery companies);

- organizations with whom we have co-promotional arrangements (and any agents used in administering such arrangements);

Yoybuy does not provide your personal information to third party organizations for their marketing purposes. We will not sell, rent or lease your personal information to others except as described in this Statement.

**Links to other web sites**

This Web Site may contain links to third party web sites. Any such linked web sites may contain their own privacy policies or statements and those third parties, and not Yoybuy, are responsible for informing you about their security and privacy practices. 

**Security**

Yoybuy value your personal information and take great effort to protect the security of your personal information. However, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed as completely secure. Yoybuy cannot ensure or warrant the 100% security of your information. We will try our best to protect your information, but you are at your own risk. 

**Changes to this statement**

Yoybuy will post any changes to this Privacy Statement on this Web Site, please check our Privacy Statement from time to time. 

**Contact details**

If you have any comments or questions about our Privacy Statement, please send E-mail to **service@yoybuy.com.**

Office in China: Beijing YOYBUY Network Technology Limited Liability Co., Ltd.Room 1406, Fl. 14, No.4, Courtyard 19, Huangping Road, Huilongguan Town, Changping District, Beijing

Office in UK:  Sunlight(UK) Trading Limited

Address: Old Street 167 City Road London, EC1V 1AW, UK

**The website follows the UK laws**
